Guide to the Graham Arthur Barden Papers, 1934-1960
Graham Arthur Barden papers 1934-1960
- Subject Series
  - A. Third District Projects and Constituent Concerns
    - Housing Administration, 1941-1960 (Folder 87-91)
    - (Box 16, Folder 92)
      Includes Federal Housing Administration,; National Housing Agency, and Public Housing Administration. Correspondence deals mainly with Barden's efforts to help constituents with loans and to aid Third District towns gain Federal assistance for housing shortages created by nearby military bases.
    - Hull Swamp Project, 1935-1936 (Folder 93)
    - Hunting--Laws and Regulations, ca. 1935-1960 (Folder 93-94)
    - Hurricane Disaster, 1952-1959 (Folder 94-96)
    - Inauguration, 1947, 1953, 1956-1957 (Folder 96-97)
    - Indian Schools Project, 1940-1942 (Folder 97)
    - Inland Waterway Property Disposal Project, 1956-1957
    - Institute of Government (Chapel Hill) Project, 1935 (Folder 98)
    - Insurance, 1958-1959
      Protects from N. C. insurance companies concerning decisions by the Army and Air Force to become self-insurers. Internal Revenue Service, 1959-1960 Most correspondence deals with IRS rules concerning extensions for filing.
    - Interior, Department of, 1936, 1944-1960 (Folder 98)
    - (Box 17, Folder 99-100)
      Most correspondence concerns fees and commercial facilities on the Blue Ridge Parkway
    - Interstate Commerce Commission, ca. 1952-1958 (Folder 100)
    - Jacksonville Community Building Project, 1936, 1939-1940 (Folder 101)
    - Jacksonville Court House Project, 1935
    - Jacksonville Gymnasium Project, 1935
    - Jacksonville Hospital Project, 1941-1945
    - Jacksonville Housing Project, 1941-1943 (Folder 101-103)
    - Jacksonville Paving Project, 1935-1936 (Folder 103)
    - Jacksonville Recreation Facilities (USO), 1946-1947 (Box 17, Folder 103)
    - Jacksonville School Project, 1940-1942 (Folder 103-104)
    - Jacksonville Sewer and Water Project, 1936-1937 (Folder 104)
    - Jasper Teacherage Project, 1936
    - Jones County Court House Project, 1935-1940 (Folder 104)
    - (Box 18, Folder 105)
      Correspondence concerns efforts to obtain funds to build a new courthouse in Jones County.
    - Joshua Creek Drainage Project, 1947 (Folder 105)
    - Judgeship, 1945
    - Justice, Department of, 1958-1960
    - Kenansville Projects
      - 1936 :: Library Project
      - 1937: Cemetery Project
    - Labor Camp Project, 1948
      Correspondence centers on efforts to establish a labor camp at Bayboro, N. C.
    - Labor, Department of, 1935, 1950-1959
    - Libraries (North Carolina), 1957-1959 (Folder 106)
    - Library (Depository), 1953
      Material concerns designating the library at New Bern a government documents depository for the Third District.
    - Library of Congress, 1952-1960
      Includes lists of books lent by LC to Barden's staff.
    - Light Houses, 1935-1939 (Folder 107)
    - Lowlands Projects (Folder 108)
      - 1935-1936: Community Building Project
      - 1939-1940: Post Office
    - Lumber Code, 1935
    - Lyon Swamp Drainage Project, 1944
    - MacArthur Firing, 1951
    - Magnolia High School 1952
    - Mail Service (to replace #48 and #49 Highway Post Office) 1959 (Folder 109)
    - Marine Corps, 1941-1949, 1960
    - Maritime Commission 1960
    - Marketing Centers, 1941
      Material concerns centers for the War Department to buy food and goods for various military camps.
    - Marketing Research, 1951
    - Maysville Projects
      - 1935: School Project
      - 1941-1942: Water and Sewer Project
    - Menhaden Fishing Industry, 1960 (Folder 110)
    - Merchant Marine and Fisheries Committee, 1938
      Material discusses ways the Federal government could aid fishermen and oystermen.
    - Mid-East North Carolina Airport, 1956-1957
    - Milk, 1942-1944 (Box 19, Folder 111-112)
      Correspondence concerns crisis in the dairy industry caused by high costs, and low prices imposed by the Office of Price Administrations
    - Monuments and Markers, 1954-1955 (Folder 112)
    - Moore's Creek Battleground, 1935-1936, 1947-1959 (Folder 112-113)
    - Morehead City Airport Project 1936 (Folder 113)
    - Morehead City Curb Market, 1940, 1945
    - Morehead City Hospital Project, 1942-1947 (Folder 113-114)
    - Morehead City Library Project, 1936, 1939 (Folder 114)
    - Morehead City Paving Project, 1939-1940
    - Morehead City School Project, 1947
    - Morehead City USO Building, Purchase of, 1947-1948
    - Mosquito Control, 1952-1960 (Folder 114-115)
      Includes 1957report of the North Carolina Salt Marsh Mosquito Study Commission.
    - Mount Olive, Town of, 1956-1960 (Folder 116)
    - Mount Olive Airport, 1946
    - Mount Olive Potato Curing House Project, 1937
    - Mount Olive Sewer Project, 1935-1936
    - Muster Out Pay, 1943-1945
    - Nahunta Swamp Project, 1937
    - National Flower, 1959
    - National Guard 1949-1950, 1954, 1957-1960 (Folder 116)
    - (Box 20, Folder 117)
      Material includes Federal assistance to National Guard to build armories, discussion over size and status of NG, and 1957 controversy caused by Sec. of Defense Wilson's statement referring to the NG as draft dodging business.
    - National Parks, 1959 (Folder 117)
      Includes pictures of proposed Clingman's Dome tower in the Great Smoky Mountain National Park.
    - National Production Authority, 1951-1952 (Folder 117-118)
    - National Recovery Act, 1935 (Folder 119)
    - National Service Life Insurance Dividends, 1950-1952
    - National War Agencies, 1943-1947 (Folder 120-121)
    - (Box 21-22, Folder 122-129)
      Correspondence related to Barden's efforts to serve as an intermediary between his constituents and various Federal agencies concerned with all aspects of World War II.
    - National Youth Administration, 1935-1943 (Folder 130-131)
    - Naval Section Base, 1941-1942 (Folder 131)
    - Navy, Department of ca. 1935-1959 (Folder 131-133)
    - New Bern, City of, 1954-1960 (Folder 133)
    - New Bern Airport, ca. 1935-1951 (Folder 134)
    - 1952-1957: Amber #9 (Box 23, Folder 135-136)
    - New Bern Armory Project, 1936-1937 (Folder 137)
      Material includes photographs of armory dedication with Barden present
    - New Bern Athletic Field, 1938
    - New Bern Auditorium Project, 1935, 1938
    - New Bern Cannery Building, 1940-1943
    - New Bern 250th Celebration, 1959-1960 (Folder 138)
    - New Bern Cemetery Project (Cedar Grove), 1937
    - New Bern Colored Library Project, 1943-1944
    - New Bern Community Center Project, 1946
    - New Bern Court House and Jail Cleaning Project, 1937-1939
    - New Bern Curb Market Project, 1938
    - New Bern Gymnasium and Community Building Project, 1938-1940 (Folder 139)
    - New Bern Harbor Project, 1937-1938
    - New Bern Health Center Project, 1942-1943
    - New Bern Hospital Project, 1942-1946, 1956 (Folder 139-140)
    - New Bern Housing Project, 1940-1944, 1954 (Box 24, Folder 141)
    - New Bern Library Project, 1935
    - New Bern Lunch Room Project, 1945
    - New Bern Miscellaneous Projects, 1935-1936
    - New Bern, National Avenue Improvement, 1943-1946
    - New Bern National Cemetery Project, 1936-1938
    - New Bern Recreation Center Project, 1941-1944 (Folder 141-142)
    - New Bern Recreation Facilities, USO, 1945-1947 (Folder 142)
    - New Bern Rent Control Office, 1943-1951
    - New Bern Schools, 1945, 1952-1960 (Folder 143)
    - New Bern Veterans Project, 1947
    - New Bern Water and Light Project, 1938-1943
    - New Bern Yacht Basin Project, 1935-1936 (Folder 144)
    - New Bern Youth Center Project, 1940-1942
    - New River Works Progress Administration, 1938n
    - Newport Gymnasium and Tennis Court Project, ca. 1935-1940
    - Newport River Project, 1937
    - Newport Water and Sewer Project, 1942
    - Newspaper Correspondence, 1935-1936
    - Newton Grove School Project, 1942-1943
    - North Carolina, State of, 1950-1960 (Folder 145-146)
    - North Carolina Delegation, 1935-1936 (Folder 146)
    - North Carolina Emergency Relief Administration, 1935-1936
    - North Carolina Highways and State Highway Commission, ca. 1935-1960 (Box 25, Folder 147-149)
    - North Carolina Organizations, 1953-1959 (Folder 149)
    - North Carolinians in Washington, 1935 (Folder 150)
    - Oak Island Coast Guard Channel, 1947
    - Office of Price Stabilization, 1951-1952
    - (Folder 151-152)
    - Office of Production Management, 1942-1943
    - (Box 26-27, Folder 153-161)
      Material reflects Barden's efforts to aid constituents in their dealings with OPM and OPM regulations.
    - Oil and Fuel, 1947-1948 (Folder 162)
      Correspondence concerns fuel shortages in the Third District.
    - Old Age Assistance, 1936-1940, 1949-1959 (Folder 162-164)
    - (Folder 165)
      Barden assists elderly in obtaining assistance from the Federal government.
    - Onslow County Projects (Folder 165)
      - 1935-1937, 1953: School Projects
      - 1939: Cemetery Project
      - 1956: Drainage Project
    - Oriental Bridge Project, 1936-1939
    - Oysters, 1935, 1946-1954 (Folder 166-167)
      Correspondence concerns a private bill to allow compensation to oyster farmers for the killing of oysters caused by the discharge of sewerage and waste from military bases.
    - Pamlico Coast Guard (USS), 1935-1940 (Folder 168)
    - Pamlico County Playgrounds Project, 1940
    - Pamlico County Wood Cutting Project, 1936
    - Passports and Visas (sample), 1953-1956 (Folder 169)
    - Patents, ca. 1951-1957
    - Peanuts, 1954-1960
    - Pender County Projects (Folder 170)
      - 1935: Court House Project
      - 1938: Sanitary Project
    - Penderlea, 1935-1939 (Folder 170)
    - (Box 29, Folder 171-174)
      Penderlea was a homesteading project in which Barden was greatly interested. Material includes 1935 financial records, and a pamphlet, Southern Rural Life- The Problem, The Solution, as well as correspondence on the project and its problems.
    - Pharmacy Corps Bill and Correspondence, 1942-1943 (Folder 175)
    - Pickles, 1935-1940
    - Pigeons 1958
    - Pikeville Water and Sewer Project, 1936-1939, 1942 (Folder 176)
    - Pine Lumber Company, 1935-1938
    - Piney Grove Playground Project, 1936
    - Pinners Point, 1938
    - Plywood, 1954, 1959
    - Port Terminal and Beaufort Railroad, 1935-1938 (Box 30, Folder 177-179)
    - Post Office Department 1959-1960 (Folder 179)
    - Postwar Projects--North Carolina, 1944-1947
    - Potatoes, ca. 1934-1958 (Folder 180-182)
    - (Box 31, Folder 183-187)
      Correspondence reflects Barden's efforts to assist potato farmers in their dealings with the Federal government in such matters as production and transportation.
    - Poultry, 1959-1960 (Folder 187)
    - Price Ceilings and War Production Board Regulations, 1944-1947 (Box 31, Folder 187-188)
    - Prisoner of War Labor, 1944-1945 (Box 32, Folder 189)
    - Public Assistance, 1958-1959
    - Public Works Administration Projects Lists 1935-1936
    - Publications--Sample Letters, 1938-1940, 1950-1958 (Folder 189-190)
      Samples of letters mailed to Third District residents offering various publications for their use.
    - Quartermaster's Depot Project 1941 (Folder 190)
    - Radioactive Waste, Disposal of, 1959 (Folder 191)
    - Railroad, 1950
    - Recommendations, 1954-1960 (Folder 191-192)
      Includes letters of recommendation for blacks and whites
    - Reconstruction Finance Corporation, 1950-1953 (Folder 193)
    - Rent Control, 1951-1953
    - Reserve Officer Corps, 1934-1935
    - Reserve Officer Training Corps, 1950-1954
    - Resettlement Administration, 1935-1938 (Folder 194)
    - Richlands Community House Project, 1935-1938 (Box 33, Folder 195)
    - Richlands Library Project, 1935-1938
    - Richlands Sewer Project, 1935-1936
    - Rivers and Harbors--Wilmington, N. C., District, Project Index and Maps, 1938, 1939 (Folder 195-196)
    - Roads: (Folder 196-199)
      - Belgrade to Swansboro Highway, 1940 (Folder 196)
      - Cartaret County Roads, 1938
      - Cape Lookout Road, 1935-1936
      - Cedar Island Road Project, 1935
      - Cotton Road Landscaping Project, 1939
      - Craven County, Route #101, 1938-1940
      - Dover-New Bern Road, 1935
      - Fort Barnwell-Dover Road Project, 1938
      - Goldsboro-Fayetteville Road, 1938
      - Harkers Island Road and Bridge, 1936-1940 (Folder 197)
      - Jones County Road, 1935, 1939
      - Lowland Road Project, 1938-1940
      - Lukens Road Project 1938
      - Marshallburg Road, 1935-1936
      - Merriman Road Project, 1936-1938
      - Mill Creek Road, 1938-1939
      - Minnesott Beach Road Project, 1937-1938 (Folder 198)
      - Mount Olive Road, 1935-1936
      - Moore's Creek Battleground Road, 1935
      - Onslow County Road Project, 1939
      - Oriental to Minnesott Road, 1938
      - Pender County Highway #53, 1940
      - Plymouth to Minnesott Beach Road, 1941
      - Reelsboro Road, 1938
      - Rose Hill Road, 1940
      - St. Helena Road Project, 1936
      - Smyrna Road Project, 1937
      - Sneads Ferry Road and Bridge, 1935-1936 (Folder 199)
      - Topsail Road Project, 1937
      - Vanceboro Road, 1935
      - Warsaw to Wallace Road, 1935
      - Roanoke River, 1955
    - Rose Hill, City of, 1939, 1954-1955, 1960
    - Rose Hill Cold Storage, 1937, 1941
    - Rose Hill Packing Company, 1944-1946 (Folder 200)
    - Roseboro Agricultural Building Project, 1936
    - Rural Electrification Administration, 1935-1957 (Folder 200)
    - (Box 34-35, Folder 201-208)
      Most of correspondence deals with Barden's aid to Third District communities in helping them to get electricity. Includes maps and statistics. Some excellent letters (especially 1955 ) on Barden's dealings with REA and various power corporations, including Carolina Power and Light Company and Tarheel Electric Membership Association. 1954 --progress report on REA in N. C. 1957 -- pamphlet, Facts about Four County Electric Membership Corporation.
    - Rural Electrification Administration:; Jones Onslow Electric Membership Corporation, ca. 1941-1957 (Folder 209-210)
    - Salemburg School Project, 1939 (Folder 211)
    - Sampson County Projects
      - 1937: Building Cleaning Project
      - 1937-1939: Court House Project
      - 1940: Sewing Room Project
      - 1950: Health Center
    - Scholarships, 1959-1960
    - Secretaries, ca. 1938-1943 (Folder 211-212)
      Letters of application for the position of secretary to Barden, 1939 --most of correspondence concerns Tom McGee's heart attack and recovery, Some correspondence between Barden and McGee about Third District matters.
    - Seed Loan Bill 1934-1936 (Folder 212)
    - Segregation, 1941, 1954-1960 (Box 36, Folder 213-216)
      1941 --essay on Benjamin Franklin and the Jews, 1954-1960 includes much printed material--speeches and essays--opposing racial integration, with some hate literature against the blacks. Barden shows no hesitancy to express his views, opposing integration and Federal interference in public (i.e. state-controlled) schools. 1955 --reprint of Frank Porter Graham article from Virginia Quarterly Review on segregation, autographed with a personal note to Barden.
    - Selective Service, 1941-1946, 1949-1959 (Folder 216-218)
    - (Box 37, Folder 219-220)
      Most correspondence deals with attempts to obtain agricultural deferments for draftees.
    - Sewage Disposal, 1960 (Folder 220)
    - Shaken Creek Project, 1939
    - Shipyards, 1940-1943 (Folder 221)
    - Small Business Administration, 1954-1959 (Folder 222)
    - Smith Creek Bridge Project, 1937-1939
    - Smyrna Gymnasium Project 1937-1939
    - Smyrna School Project, 1940-1942 (Folder 223)
    - Sneads Ferry Breakwater Project, 1958
    - Sneads Ferry Sewing Project, 1938
    - Social Security, 1952-1960 (Folder 223-224)
    - (Folder 225)
      Barden assists constituents in dealing with Social Security regulations and eligibility requirements.
    - Socialized Medicine, 1949 1951-1952, 1954 (Box 38, Folder 225-226)
      Correspondence and resolutions reflecting public opinion on a national health insurance plan.
    - Soil Conservation Checks, 1937-1938 (Folder 226-228)
      Correspondence shows Barden's assistance to constituents having problems with governmental red tape. Some material concerns tobacco acreage allotments.
    - Soil Erosion--Neuse River, 1945 (Folder 228)
    - Soil Surveys, ca 1953-1960
      Material includes annual reports of the Lower Neuse Conservation District (1952) and the Southeastern Soil Conservation District (1953, 1959 )
    - Southeastern Power Administration, 1951-1952 (Folder 229-230)
    - Soybeans, 1955, 1957 (Box 39, Folder 231)
    - State Department, ca. 1948-1959
    - Stonewall Auditorium Project, 1940
    - Stoney Creek Drainage Project, 1936
    - Straits Athletic Field Project, 1936-1937
    - Strawberries, 1944-1946 (Folder 231-232)
    - Sugar, 1944-1947 (Folder 233)
      Material relating to governmental rationing of sugar and constituents' problems in dealing with the regulations.
    - Supreme Court, 1958-1959
    - Surplus Commodities Corporation, 1937-1940 (Folder 233-234)
    - Surplus Marketing, 1941-1942 (Folder 235)
    - Surplus Property, 1944-1950, 1955-1958 (Folder 235-236)
    - (Box 40, Folder 237-242)
      Barden aids constituents in obtaining surplus government property (e.g. land, buildings, and goods).
    - Swanaboro Recreation Center Project, 1947 (Box 41, Folder 243)
    - Swanaboro U. S. O., 1941, 1943
    - Swanaboro Water and Sewer, 1938-1939, 1941-1943, 1947 (Folder 243-244)
    - Sweet Potatoes, 1945 (Folder 244)
    - Swift Creek Drainage Project, 1935-1939, 1956
    - Tar River Drainage Project, 1935 (Folder 245)
    - Tariff, 1956-1957, 1959-1960
      Material includes report ( February 1957) entitled Supplemental Cotton Textile Tariff Study.
    - Tax on Federal Land, 1952
    - Telephones, 1952-1955-1958
    - Tobacco, 1935-1960 (Folder 246- 248)
    - (Box 42-43, Folder 249-256)
      Correspondence generally reflects Barden's assistance to Third District constituents in dealing with governmental regulations concerning such matters as tobacco acreage allotments transportation, and marketing.
    - Tobacco Cloth, Flue and Twine, 1945-1947, 1950 (Folder 256-258)
    - Tobacco Markets, 1945-1949 (Folder 258-259)
      Material concerns developing and maintaining tobacco markets at New Bern, Wallace, and Goldsboro.
    - Town Creek Project, 1938 (Folder 259)
    - Trent River Bridge Project, 1951-1952
    - Trent River Dredging Project, 1940-1941
    - Truck Applications, 1943-1945 (Folder 260)
    - (Box 44, Folder 261-264)
      Correspondence deals with constituents' attempts to purchase trucks and the restrictions on such purchases imposed by the Federal government during World War II.
    - Tryon Palace, 1939-1940 (Folder 264)
      Correspondence concerns attempts to develop Tryon Palace as an historic site. Efforts were later halted by World War II.
    - United Nations, 1954-1958
    - Vanceboro Projects
      - 1935-1936: Sewer Project
      - 1936: Bridge Project
      - 1940: Recreational Project
      - 1957, 1959: Vanceboro, City of
    - Vandemere Projects (Folder 265)
      - 1938: Oyster Planting Project
      - 1938: Streets Project
    - Veterans Hospital Project, 1947-1949
    - Veterans Life Insurance, 1954
    - Vocational Rehabilitation Program, 1944-1945, 195S (Folder 266)
    - Voice of America, 1951-1953
      Letters in May, 1952, concern the Voice of America and its connections with F. E. Carlyle's political campaign.
    - Wallace Projects (Box 44, Folder 266)
      - 1938, 1941: Community Building
      - 1940: School Project
      - 1942: Canneries Project
    - War Claims Commission, 1950-1953
    - War, Department of, 1935-1936, 1939 (Folder 266)
    - (Box 45, Folder 267)
      Correspondence generally concerns Barden's aid to veterans in obtaining duplicate discharge certificates and his assistance to local communities in scheduling Army units (e.g. bands, airplanes) for special celebrations.
    - Warsaw: Stewart Creek Project, 1936 (Folder 268)
    - Water Rights and Water Pollution, 1959
      Material includes booklet and addresses: Comprehensive Pollution Abatement Plan for the Cape Fear River Basin, Federal Encroachment on State Water Rights (an address by Clarence A. Davis, former Solicitor and Under Secretary of the Interior), and State Versus Federal Water Rights (an address by Burnham Enersen).
    - Wayne County Memorial Community Building, 1941, 1943, 1945
    - Wayne County Projects (Folder 269)
      - 1940: Court House
      - 1953: Critical Defense Housing Area
      - 1954: Drought Relief
      - 1956: Drainage Project
    - Wayne County Schools, 1935-1938, 1956-1960
    - Wayne County Veterans Hospital, 1937-1938 (Folder 270)
    - Western Union, 1951 (Folder 271)
    - White House Conference on Children and Youth, 1959
    - White House Mementos, 1951-1952
    - White Oak River Project, 1938-1939
    - Wild Life Resources Commission, ca. 1945-1957
    - Wilmington: Critical Defense Housing Area, 1951
    - Wilson Stadium, 1939
    - Work Relief, 1935
    - Works Progress Administration, 1935-1943 (Folder 271-272)
    - (Box 46, Folder 273-278)
      Material includes notices of the passage of Third District projects and miscellaneous correspondence concerning various projects. October 7, 1935 --outline of the Federal Writers Project. February, 1936 --list of WPA projects for the Third District with their costs, descriptions, and sponsor's justifications.
    - Yacht Basin Project--Morehead City, 1940 (Folder 278)
  - B. Military
    - 1. Installations
      - Air Direction Center Calypso, N. C., 1958 (Box 47, Folder 279)
      - Cherry Point, ca. 1941-1954 (Folder 280-286)
      - Cherry Point, ca. 1955-1960 (Box 48, Folder 287-288)
      - Cherry Point:
        - Access Bridge, 1951-1952 (Folder 289)
        - New Bern School, 1949-1955 (Folder 290)
        - Apprentice School, 1952-1955 (Folder 291)
        - Planner & Estimator Dispute, 1954 (Folder 292)
        - Fuel, 1956 (Folder 293)
        - Quonset Huts, 1956-1957 (Folder 294)
        - Power Plant, 1958-1959 (Folder 295)
      - Camp Davis, Hollyridge, N. C. (Folder 296-297)
      - Camp Davis (Box 49, Folder 298-300)
      - Camp Lejeune--Cherry Point Railroad (Folder 301-304)
      - Camp Lejeune--Cherry Point Railroad (Box 50, Folder 305-306)
      - Camp Lejeune Railroad:; ICC Hearings, 1955-1959 (Folder 307)
      - Camp Lejeune: (Folder 308)
        - Walmor Hotel, 1951
        - Bombing & Shelling, 1955-1959 (Folder 309)
        - Theaters, 1956 (Folder 310)
        - Air Facility Housing, 1957-1958 (Folder 311-312)
        - Post Exchange, 1958 (Folder 313)
        - Miscellaneous (Folder 314-315)
      - Camp Lejeune: Miscellaneous (Box 51, Folder 316)
      - Seymour Johnson Air Force Base, Goldsboro, N. C., 1941-1960 (Folder 317-321)
      - Seymour Johnson (Box 52, Folder 322-328)
      - Seymour Johnson (Box 53, Folder 329)
      - Seymour Johnson Field, 1945. (Folder 330)
        Notebook, 29 pp. with maps of Goldsboro and the air base. Correspondence about establishment, expansion, and maintenance of the base
      - Analysis, Preliminary Master Plan for Seymour Johnson Field, March 1947, 13 pp. (Folder 331)
      - Seymour Johnson Field, Supplemental Brief May 25, 1947. 100 pages (Folder 332)
      - In re Seymour Johnson Field, 1948 (Folder 333)
      - Seymour Johnson Air Force Base. Prepared for Subcommittee of Senate and House Conferees Sept. 20, 1951. (Folder 334)
      - Seymour Johnson Field and Goldsboro, N. C. Photographs (ca 100) (Folder 335)
      - Seymour Johnson Field. July 14, 1951. With Photographs. (Box 54, Folder 336)
      - Goldsboro, N. C, Photographs, ca. 1951 (Folder 337)
      - Comments on Seymour Johnson (Folder 338-339)